ジューキャロン
Oh
See you next time.
Captain, may I ask you a question?
And Queen to F3.
Alright. King to G7.
Is it a good idea to send me into battle?
Rook to E4.
If I should get killed, the Deucalion's Alt-Noah will shut down.
Yes, I'm aware of that. Rook to D8.
But we can't worry about that until we have to.
And Zenkaiska, are you trying to ask if you can be relieved of combat duty?
No. I'm really well suited for it.
Now Queen to F6 and check.
King to F6. King takes your Queen.
And I would agree with your assessment.
Bishop to E5. Check.
I'll put it on the monitor.
Did you come up with that move all by yourself?
Or is it from that analytical engine of yours?
70% at least is me.
70%?
I'm trying to optimize its processing efficiency by assigning tasks to idle brain cells.
So it's the device's suggestion as well as my own organic idea at the same time.
Both this ship and everyone in her crew owe their lives to you.
If you believe you should be fighting, I think we should accept your judgment on that.
Thanks for that.
But I don't deserve any kind of special treatment.
Has anyone told you that all Noah activation tests were conducted using samples of the blood splatter from your clothing?
Hmm?
King to G5.
All unsuccessful.
None met the requirements for powering up.
You are a special case indeed, Ensign.
The activation factor you received when you administered emergency treatment was somehow triggered when it came into contact with Royal Blood.
Ever since the last battle, we've obtained plenty of intel on both the Martian cataphracts as well as their use of Aldnoa.
For military power, no question they have the advantage over us.
If we take them on, we'll surely be the underdogs.
If we do, Ensign Kaizka, then my money is on you.
Bishop to G7.
Do you resign, Captain?
Was that a move from you or your left eye?
I'll let you decide that for yourself.
Well, I suppose not even the Tharsis can see that far into the future.
Carry on.
Yes, sir.
And were you successful, my lord Slane?
I clustered my shots in the region you calculated, Mr. Parklight.
Good, my lord.
Let's hope they're not deflected by some uncharted flux.
Ah, I thought I smelled something.
Looks like a dog snuck on board.
And a common grubby little puppy dog at that.
Just what are you doing here?
Good day, Count Muril Sion.
And you too, Count Barocruz.
I came because my wish is to join the battle.
Disgusting creature.
You need to mind your tongue.
Count Sosboom?
Sir Slane Troyard here is my vassal.
If he is offended, I apologize.
However, if this action of yours is unwarranted, Count Muril Sion, it would be unfortunate.
If he were merely some pet, it would be barely tolerable.
But to actually make him a knight, that's taking your game a little too far.
Count Barocruz, you do not have the privilege of offering opinions regarding my vassals.
Fighting alongside him is another matter entirely.
One cannot take to the field of battle with a traitor at your back.
Well then, go ahead and strike me down right now.
You are entirely correct.
If I went into battle with you, it's almost certain I would be struck from behind.
How dare you!
Everyone, hear my words!
By the grace of the Emperor of Verse, here and now I name the knight slain Troyard as my son.
Every one of you here bears witness to this!
My lord count-
Stand, Slane.
From this day forward, you are my son.
And do you still wish to raise a hand to him now, Count Muril Sion?
If you are prepared to go to such lengths, then so be it.
But if his behavior is suspicious in the slightest, there will be no mercy.
Forgive me, my lord.
I have put you in an awkward position.
No.
I had decided on this long ago.
I too could fall in battle.
I must have a successor in place.
So from now on, think of me as your father.
Congratulations, my lord Slane.
Heir to Count Salzbaum.
This change puts you one step closer to your dream, my lord.
That is enough, Mr. Harklight.
Someone in my position has no dreams.
The time has almost come.
Yes, my lady.
Which side do you think will emerge victorious, Adele Ritzo?
Why, the glorious First Imperial Forces will absolutely win the day.
Of course.
Is that really what you want?
Don't you have friends down on Earth aboard a United Forces ship?
Friends down on Earth?
Oh, perish the thought.
Well then, how about a wager?
A wager?
If the Verse Empire wins, I bet...
Let me think.
I know.
I bet my sister's life.
I'm joking.
I wonder...
What are you dreaming of now, dear sister?
Hey, have you seen Inko?
Try the Electromat Catapult.
She and Raya are probably hanging out there.
That's great.
Thanks a bunch!
And try not to get lost.
Bye!
Damn!
Wearing sweats!
Yutaro, you know you're a pervert, right?
Tharsis.
Full ability is still unknown.
High percentage of attack evasion reported.
Current pilot has been confirmed.
Slane, Troiard.
A good luck charm given to me by a dear Terran friend when I left for Earth.
Animals that fly through the air!
Yes, Slane, it's just like you told me.
Does he also have a Neuralink?
An analytical engine of his own?
Must be.
But I don't have enough data.
It was dodging like it could see the future.
If that's the way things are, could be a problem.
You monologuing?
Just talking to myself.
That's what monologuing is!
The warrior god Odin, the rider of the eight-legged horse Sleipnir, drank the waters of Mimus Bruner and was granted vast wisdom.
But the price he paid for gaining that wisdom was his left eye.
Norse mythology.
You're quite the nerd.
Oh man, now you're just messing with me, right?
After that Russian battle we had, I just wanted to get off the ship.
I was scared to death.
But I knew if I did that, I could never look Okujo in the eye when I died.
If your horse is ever acting up, you find me day or night.
And I'll fix it up in a flash.
I'll hold you to that.
Alright, look.
Why don't we grab a bite before the battle?
We should have enough time for it.
I'll pass, thanks.
Back when I got shot, apparently my stomach was empty.
I'd have died if my other organs had been contaminated by what was in my stomach.
Really?
Ugh.
But considering, some tea would be good.
Has he chosen his wire reels yet?
Number one through number three.
Number ten in case of emergency.
One of each mounted left and right.
His specs are showing some high-G pivots.
Long, thin wires aren't optimal for that.
I found you!
If it isn't Team Decalian...
The old Noah unit everyone's on about.
They say that you're all Martians.
You don't want to get in our way on the battlefield, little ladies.
Stupid jerks.
What's their problem anyway?
But they aren't wrong.
All Martians are the enemy.
I know that better than anyone.
You are so adorable, Rae.
Hard shell outside.
I'm what?
With a soft, gooey center.
What are you talking about?
Want to get some candy?
I'm gonna deck you.
Entering defense airspace in 30 minutes.
Clear to initiate launch.
Launch.
And good hunting.
Is my steed prepared?
All fine-tuning completed, my lord.
Good.
Teoscuria 2, launching!
Sir Slain Troyard, now launching the Tharsis.
Stygia Squadron, launching!
Martian cataphracts on approach.
Attention all forces!
We are go for action!
Message from headquarters.
We are a go for action.
Deucalion, launch now.
We will be providing guerrilla-style support for the attack platoons.
Prepare the ship for battle.
All our shipboard cataphracts.
They're being launched from Trident Base.
Mustang-1-1, you are clear for launch.
Roger that.
Mustang-1-1, cleared for launch confirmed.
Railgun launch!
Target lock is in effect.
Now commencing the attack.
Enemy inbound!
Hold fire!
They won't be able to hit us in this gravity flux anyway.
Fire when they get in closer!
Fire when they get in closer.
My umbrella's been hit!
Mustang-1-1!
I'm okay.
Debris is bad.
I can't get a shot with this vibration!
Mustang-0-0 will assist.
Inaho!
What about your umbrella?
It's only drizzling.
I don't need it.
Stop it with your crazy stunts!
I wouldn't be able to use it in a dogfight anyway.
Infer gravity shifts.
Apply vector compensation.
Fire.
Commence attack!
Why, you?
Pivot via wire swing-by.
Returning to combat space.
Reel number three.
Fire.
Pivot in progress.
Complete in four, three, two, and one.
Release.
Inaho Kaisuka.
And you slain Troyard.
Next conjunction with Marineros' base in 30 seconds.
Main guns ready to go.
Attention all platoons.
Clear away from our line of fire.
Rye!
This is Rhinelander 2-2.
I've got one of these things right on my six.
Roger that.
Mustang 2-2 moving to assist.
It's the Martian.
Marineros' base now within range.
Field of fire is clear.
No friendlies.
Fire main guns.
Marineros' base beginning to move away.
Disengage attack platoons and guerrilla unit immediately.
Put them on defense.
Inaho, we've been ordered to disengage.
Come back.
Inaho!
That is some accurate shooting.
I knew it.
He's using predictions.
Number one, pivot.
I'll wait until the moment he comes out from behind the rocks.
He will attack me the instant that I leave the protection of the rocks.
Data confirmed.
Two minutes to impact.
Let's go.
And fire.
What?
I hit him?
Is that...
Are you all right, Slane?
You should fall back.
No, I can still fight.
Don't overdo it.
This orange one.
I owe him some payback.
That gap in my barrier?
I decided to change its location.
Fly now, my servants!
If I can walk.
The white one...
Is that...
No!
No.
Energy joints linked, blade field engaged.
Blade drawn.
No escape.
Inaho, I'll cover you! Get away from it!
You need to stay back, Inko.
No!
Stay there.
Right at that position.
Prepare to meet your doom, Terran!
Right kick thruster.
Jettison.
Fire!
The flames aren't going in there!
The barrier gap!
Stop him!
Selene, help!
What's that?
Moving debris cluster.
I picked up a cloud of it, closing at high speed on my 3D Doppler radar.
Thank you, Inko. A split second later. And I would likely have been caught in it.
Ridiculous!
My Dio Scuria disabled by mere rock debris?!
That was not debris!
Huh?
It was bullets.
I fired them before the battle even began.
I calculated it so they would go around the earth and intersect that spot at that very moment.
What?
Originally, it was a trap to defeat Inaho Kaisuka. The trick was to disable your dimensional barrier. And I thought that he might be able to do it.
But Slane!
Shut up!
Did you honestly believe that I could ever swear true fealty to you?
To the man who plotted to kill Princess Asalem? Did you think I could ever forgive you?
The second barrage is on its way. Goodbye now.
Goodbye now.
Father.
Nicely played.
On this day, I have lost my second father. The prosperity of the Verse Empire was his life's devotion. I now give you my word, his legacy will not die. I will carry on the work my father began, for even greater prosperity.
Lords of the Verse Orbital Knights, this is no time for petty squabbles. As Knights of the Noble Verse Empire, should we not work as one? To eradicate the vile resistance forces of Earth? In the name of her Imperial Highness Asalem Versalusia, let us punish the jury.
Interesting. He is telling the truth.
Huh?
We're at our lunar base. Her Highness Asalem has been fighting for time.
I knew it. She's still alive.
My lord, that was a great speech that you made.
Tell me, Mr. Harklight, were you born into the third class?
I was. Though they were very poor and of a lower class, my father and mother worked hard to raise me, and used every means at their disposal to place me with the Orbital Knights.
My lord slain, it is for that very reason I offer you my utmost respect. You have attained the rank of Count, though you were born a Terran.
This new era will be for us.
Harklight, let's begin.
Yes.
Count slain Sosbaum Troyard.
Sosbaum Troyard.
Heroes Everyone.
Sosie of es richtlaage.
Sos qualcosa
I'm looking for a future
I'm looking for a light in the sky
I'm looking for a light
Even if you're alive
Even if you're perfect
I'm looking for a light
Just live straight
Every time you shoot
What if I am wrong but far still
I will climb up the
Thank you.